// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who was the first woman to be a pilot in Nigeria?",
    answer: "Mrs. Chinyere Onyemucheya",
    options: [
      "Nkojo Iweala",
      "Mrs Fela Kuti",
      "Mrs. Chinyere Onyemucheya",
      "Lt. Miriam Ahmed"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who was the youngest judge in the world?",
    answer: "John Payton",
    options: [
      "John Payton",
      "Jonas Wick",
      "Ramson Nathaniel",
      "Frank Bullin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What system has the function of Head of state & Head of Government in an individual?",
    answer: "Presidential System",
    options: [
      "Parliamentary System",
      "Unitary System",
      "Presidential System",
      "Federal System"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who founded the first political party in Nigeria?",
    answer: "Herbert Macaulay",
    options: [
      "Herbert Macaulay",
      "Nnamdi Azikiwe",
      "Olusegun Obasanjo",
      "Muhammed Buhari"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does the eagle on Nigerian court of Arm represent?",
    answer: "Strength",
    options: [
      "Authority",
      "Unity",
      "Strength",
      "Courage"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Who among the following is the first Asian American to feature on US currency?",
  answer: "Anna May Wong",
  options: [
    "Swadesh Chetta",
    "Anna May Wong",
    "Kamala Harrison",
    "Kim Chui"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
question: "Who was the first American to win a noble Peace Price?",
answer: "Theodore Roosevelt",
options: [
  "Abraham Lincoln",
  "George Bush Sr.",
  "Theodore Roosevelt",
  "Franklin Roosevelt"
]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: "Which bank of US collapsed in March 2023",
answer: "Citigroup",
options: [
  "Citigroup",
  "Goldman Sach",
  "JP Morgan Chase",
  "Silicon Valley Bank"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: "Which US building was stormed by protesters on 7th January 2021?",
answer: "Capitol",
options: [
  "Capitol",
  "Supreme Court",
  "Pentagon",
  "White House"
]
},
{
numb: 10,
question: "US president Joe Biden has also served as?",
answer: "Vice President",
options: [
  "Director CIA",
  "Speaker",
  "Secretary State",
  "Vice President"
]
},
{
numb: 11,
question: "Airbnb is an American______ company?",
answer: "Home-rental",
options: [
  "Home-rental",
  "Transportation",
  "Pharmaceutical",
  "Tire manufacturing"
]
},
{
numb: 12,
question: "Who is the current Prime Minister of UK?",
answer: "Rishi Sunak",
options: [
  "Boris Johnson",
  "Theresa May",
  "Rishi Sunak",
  "Liz Truss"
]
},
{
numb: 13,
question: "UK formally exited from European Union on?",
answer: "31 January 2019",
options: [
  "31 January 2019",
  "31 December 2019",
  "31 January 2020",
  "31 December 2020"
]
},
{
numb: 14,
question: "Bretix deal between UK and EU  was reached on 24th ______?",
answer: "December",
options: [
  "October",
  "September",
  "November",
  "December"
]
},
{
numb: 15,
question: "Which river passes through Paris?",
answer: "Seine",
options: [
  "Loire",
  "Rhine",
  "Seine",
  "Garonne"
]
},
{
numb: 16,
question: "Which lady character was a national symbol during French Republic?",
answer: "Marianne",
options: [
  "Bella",
  "Marianne",
  "Adelle",
  "Sabriel"
]
},
{
numb: 17,
question: "Which one is the longest river in France?",
answer: "Loire",
options: [
  "Rhine",
  "Seiwn",
  "Moselle",
  "Loire"
]
},
{
numb: 18,
question: "In which year were Euro bank notes and coin introduced in France?",
answer: "2002",
options: [
  "1998",
    "1999",
  "2001",
  "2002"
]
},
{
numb: 19,
question: "Who  was the first king of the House of Bourbon?",
answer: "Henry IV",
options: [
  "Henry IV",
  "Louis XIII",
  "Charles IX",
  "Louis XV"
]
},
{
numb: 20,
question: "In which year, Charles de Gaulle elected as the President of France?",
answer: "1959",
options: [
  "1943",
  "1951",
  "1959",
  "1965"
]
},
 
];
